Jordan Adriano

jordanadrianoo@gmail.com| 832.876.2911 | Houston, Texas | linkedin.com/in/Jordan-Adriano

SUMMARY

University junior specializing in Computer Science. skilled in many universal computer languages. Critical learner who can adapt to many situations or environments with ease without sacrificing efficiency or creativity. Approximately 4 years of coding both independently and as a valued team member. Created a wide variety of programs that ranged from both educational and entertaining.

EDUCATION

University of Houston-Downtown

GPA: 3.00

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

Anticipated Graduation: 05/2021

San Jacinto Community College

GPA: 3.08

Associates of Science, Computer Science

Anticipated Graduation: 12/2019

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Computer Languages:

- Java
- Python
- C/C++
- HTML
- JavaScript

Additional Skills:

- Detail orientated
- Proficient adaptability
- Strong management skills
- Fluent in Spanish (Speaking)
- · Creative and critical thinking skills

EXPERIENCE

Rice University Server – Houston, TX

Aug 2015 - Present

Senior Server

- Responsible for efficient server training seminars
- · Team leader responsible for other severs success and upward mobility
- Adapted to multiple job professions during the off semesters

HP CodeWars - Houston, TX

March 2015

Participant

- Managed team productivity during intense time limited hackathon
- Create unique, creative, and efficient algorithms to solve complex coding problems
- Composed functioning code from other team member's base algorithms

COMPUCAMP- Houston, TX

May 2014 – Aug 2014

Participant

- Studied C++ under a restricted time period.
- Studied computer organization and specifications
- Built leadership while managing a small team to compose algorithms

Telemetry Data Project, Houston, TX

Aug 2019 - Sep 2019

Data Analyst

- Programmed c# based scripts onto an Arduino Uno to harvest and analyze real-time telemetry data.
- Designed circuits to display harvested data to LCD display.